Guide to 100@100: Women composers interviewed by Mt. Holyoke College students
100@100: Women composers interviewed by Mt. Holyoke College students
Oral History of American Music
100@100: Women Composers Interviewed by Mt. Holyoke College Students - TEST13
2020 2021
100@100
Oral History of American Music
20 Computer Files
6.6 gigabytes
Ng, Tianhui
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. The finding aid includes links to stream most interviews online via Oral History of American Music's (OHAM) AV access system, Aviary. Yale users can login to Aviary using their Yale University ID, to stream these interviews without restriction. Other users are able to request access to interviews directly through Aviary. For access instructions, and to request transcripts of an interview, see OHAM's website.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by surname.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
.mp4 files
Women composers; Composers United States 21st century
- Anderson, Beth
  - Anderson, Beth, 2020 December 5; 100@100 1 a; Malnick, Lucinda; 1 Computer File; 206 megabytes; Approximate running time: 62 mins
    Interview location
    Interview conducted via videochat.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    .mp4 files
    Anderson, Beth, 1950-
- Beglarian, Eve
  - Beglarian, Eve, 2020 November 6; 100@100 8 a; Perlman, Eliana; 1 Computer File; 487 megabytes; Approximate running time: 65 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Brandon, VT and interviewer in Melbourne, FL
    .mp4 file
    Beglarian, Eve (19580722)
- Brazelton, Kitty
  - Brazelton, Kitty, 2020 November 30; 100@100 9 a; McGrath, Anna; 1 Computer File; 146 megabytes; Approximate running time: 63 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Barnstable, MA and interviewer in North Andover, MA.
    Brazelton, Kitty, 1951-
- Brouwer, Margaret
  - Brouwer, Margaret, 2020 October 28; 100@100 11 a; Levy, Dani; 1 Computer File; 126 megabytes; Approximate running time: 29 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat with interviewee in Cleveland, OH and intervierer in Frisco, TX.
    Brouwer, Margaret, 1940-
- Chen Yi
  - Chen Yi, 2021 May 25; 100@100 2 a; Sun, Jingyi; 1 Computer File; 363 megabytes; Approximate running time: 64 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Kansas City, MO
    Chen, Yi, 1953-
- Farrin, Suzanne
  - Farrin, Suzanne, 2020 November 16; 100@100 10 a; Shime, Amiko; 1 Computer File; 418 megabytes; Approximate running time: 63 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in New York, NY and interviewer in Scarsdale, NY
    Farrin, Suzanne
- Hennies, Sarah
  - Hennies, Sarah, 2021 May 3; 100@100 3 a; 1 Computer File; 526 megabytes; Approximate running time: 57 mins
    Hennies, Sarah, 1979-; Insalaco, Milena
- Lamb, Alexis
  - Lamb, Alexis, 2021 April 29; 100@100 4 a; Goldin, Emma; 1 Computer File; 562 megabytes; Approximate running time: 57 mins
    Lamb, Alexis C.
- Lash, Han
  - Lash, Han, 2020 December 12; 100@100 12 a; Wang, Amanda; 1 Computer File; 212 megabytes; Approximate running time: 48 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in New Haven, CT and interviewer in Beijing, China
    Lash, Hannah, 1981-
- Laster, Gwen
  - Laster, Gwen, 2021 April 19; 100@100 5 a; Sapini, Briana; 1 Computer File; 554 megabytes; Approximate running time: 77 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Brooklyn, NY.
    Laster, Gwen
- Mallonee, Caroline
  - Mallonee, Caroline, 2020 October 16; 100@100 16 a; Johnson, Kristen; 1 Computer File; 235 megabytes; Approximate running time: 57 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Buffalo, NY and interviewer in Haverford, PA
    Mallonée, Caroline (Caroline Joanna), 1975-
- Porter, Tanner
  - Porter, Tanner, 2020 October 31; 100@100 17 a; 1 Computer File; 441 megabytes; Approximate running time: 53 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat with interviewee in California and interviewer in Seattle, WA.
    Day, Sarah
- Shyu, Jen
  - Shyu, Jen, 2021 March 1; 100@100 18 a; Kim, Sienna; 1 Computer File; 699 megabytes; Approximate running time: 67 mins
    Shyu, Jen
- Snider, Sarah Kirkland
  - Snider, Sarah Kirkland, 2020 November 20; 100@100 13 a; Fitzgerald, Catelyn; 1 Computer File; 322 megabytes; Approximate running time: 66 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Princeton, NJ and interviewer in Emmaus, PA
    Snider, Sarah Kirkland (1973-)
- Socolofsky, Annika
  - Socolofsky, Annika, 2021 May 17; 100@100 19 a; Healy, Bryn; 1 Computer File; 400 megabytes; Approximate running time: 55 mins
    Socolofsky, Annika K., 1990-
- Stepanek, Julie
  - Stepanek, Julie, 2020 October 13; 100@100 20 a; Loomis, Richard; 1 Computer File; 118 megabytes; Approximate running time: 25 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Shutesbury, MA and interviewer in Belchertown, MA.
    Stepanek, Julie
- Tesori, Jeanine
  - Tesori, Jeanine, 2021 January 14; 100@100 14 a; Rogers, Hope (Flutist); 1 Computer File; 43.9 megabytes; Approximate running time: 48 mins
    Conditions Governing Access
    This material is restricted. Access may be granted to a patron who has obtained direct permission from the interviewee or their estate.
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in Southold, NY and interviewer in Chicago, IL
    .m4a file
    Tesori, Jeanine
- Tower, Joan
  - Tower, Joan, 2021 April 24; 100@100 6 a; Estrada, Samantha; 1 Computer File; 615 megabytes; Approximate running time: 54 mins
    Tower, Joan, 1938-
- Walker, Gwyneth
  - Walker, Gwyneth, 2020 October 30; 100@100 15 a; Myren, Isabel; 1 Computer File; 321 megabytes; Approximate running time: 53 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee in New Canaan, CT and interviewer in Pierre, SD
    Walker, Gwyneth, 1947-
- Zaimont, Judith Lang
  - Zaimont, Judith Lang, 2021 April 16; 100@100 7 a; Johnson, Kristen; 1 Computer File; 2.3 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 92 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat
    Zaimont, Judith Lang, 1945-